federalbank.co.in 2018-01-28

# Personal, NRI, Business Banking, Online Banking, Mobile Banking - Federal Bank

### Privacy Policy

At Federal Bank our principal concern is the responsible use of information that users and clients share and disclose to us. Federal Bank's commitment towards guaranteed confidentiality and privacy at all times is clearly articulated in our Privacy Policy. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private, and is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted.

####  Collecting Personal Information

We collect information that users provide voluntarily to us, in the form of feedback. Federal Bank does not provide any information of users to a third party without specifically informing the users at the time of collection or without the express consent of users themselves.

####  Use of Access Log Files

Federal Bank logs IP addresses, browser type, number of pages viewed etc. in order to provide better service for our users. We use the information to get page view statistics, to analyze trends and better understand the usage of the site, and for system administration purposes.

####  Use of User Information

Federal Bank reserves the right to perform statistical analysis of user behaviours and preferences in order to measure users' relative interests in the various areas of the web site for the purpose of product and service development. The analysis is anonymous and not tagged to identifiable users. The analytical data that Federal Bank collects is for internal use only to improve the content and services of its web site. In return, users will benefit from improved quality of services.

####  Disclosure to Third Parties

Unless Federal Bank specifically informs users at the time of collection, or unless users give express consent, Federal Bank does not provide any personally identifying information to a third party. However, if subpoenaed or ordered by a court of law, Federal Bank will have to disclose to the proper authorities the personal information of any individual user.

####  Links to Other Materials

Linked sites are not under the control of Federal Bank, and Federal Bank will not be held responsible for the content or privacy policies of any linked sites or any links containing other linked sites.

####  Updating of Privacy Policy and Consent

Federal Bank will, as and when it deems fit to do so, change, alter or modify its Privacy Policy. Users are advised to visit the site continually in order to monitor changes in the policy, as the policy will be binding upon them in relation to their use of Federal Bank 's services.

© Federal bank Limited, 2017
